Dustin Yoshiaki Daikoku

1205 N Dawes St Kennewick WA, 99336 (808)-636-4462 DDAIKOKU7@GMAIL.COM

Professional Summary

Current student at WSU: Tri-Cities majoring in Computer Science. Prior job experience in both the veterinary and human medical fields. Works well in a team and seeks an environment where everyone contributes, and the day's objectives are completed in an efficient and communicative manner. Willing and able to learn.

Education

2023

Obtained at Value Pet Clinic: Puyallup - Veterinary Medication Clerk Certificate

2021

Pima Medical Institute, Renton, WA – Veterinary Assistant Certificate

2016

U.S. Army - Basic Combat Training, Healthcare Specialist Advanced Individual Training

2016

Kalaheo High School, Kailua, HI - HS Diploma

Work Experience

2023-2024

The Fix Machine: Kennewick, WA – Veterinary Assistant

- Assisted in maintaining an efficient flow with in-processing surgery patients for a high-volume spay/neuter-based clinic
- Worked directly with the Veterinarian and transcribed all pertinent notes and data physically and digitally taken during examinations
- Maintained clinic sterility at all points throughout the day and ensured a clean and safe environment throughout the entire clinic with the assistance of all team members

2022 - 2023

Value Pet Clinic: Puyallup, Puyallup, WA – Veterinary Assistant

- Performed receptionist duties and assisted in scheduling appointments and working behind the front desk
- Prepared and dispensed medication under the veterinarian's supervision according to the treatment plan presented

- Served as the point of communication in between the client and the veterinarian and ensured that the doctor's intent and treatment was clearly presented in a clear and concise manner
- Assisted in procedures and performed treatments in accordance to the veterinarian's plan
- Took part in emergency procedures involving patients in critical conditions
- Facilitated deliveries and ensured that products were fully stocked in all areas
- Always maintained and ensures the cleanliness of the clinic regardless of patient capacity

2021 - 2022

Spanaway Veterinary Clinic, Spanaway, WA – Veterinary Assistant

- Restrained animals of varying sizes and strength
- Sterilized and prepared surgical tools and PPE
- Handled multiple different species of animals and assisted during procedures involving them
- Ensured the needs of boarded animals were being properly met
- Assisted to maintain the cleanliness of the clinic and sterility of the surgical suite.

2016 - 2020

US Army, JBLM, WA - Healthcare Specialist/Combat Medic

- Completed EMT training and the 68W Healthcare Specialist training
- Provided medical care to critical and non-critical patients
- · Performed immunizations/shots and organized the associated paperwork with them
- Maintained soldier individual soldier readiness regardless of environment or conditions

Key Skills

- Animal restraint
- Patience
- Persistence
- Teamwork
- Cleaning and maintaining